http://www.coldhardycacti.freehosting.net/terms-of-use/

Terms Of Use
This Web site is an online information and communication service provided by United Online, Inc. and its affiliated companies ("UOL"). Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using this site. By using this site you signify your agreement with these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms of Use, do not use this site. UOL reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms of Use at any time. Such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified Terms of Use. By using this site after we have posted notice of such modifications, alterations or updates, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. UOL retains the right to deny access to anyone at its complete discretion for any reason including for violation of any of these Terms of Use. This Web site provides links to many other Web sites affiliated with UOL that may have terms, conditions, and other policies that differ from the Terms of Use specified herein, particularly in the case of Web sites hosting third-party content or that allow postings by third-parties. By accessing such Web sites through links provided on this site, you agree to abide by each applicable terms, conditions, and policies as therein specified.
Trademarks, Copyrights and Restrictions
This site is controlled and operated by United Online, Inc. at 21255 Burbank Boulevard, Woodland Hills, CA. The phone number is (818) 287-3000. All material on this site, including, but not limited to, images, illustrations, audio clips, and video clips, is protected by copyrights, trademarks, and other intellectual property rights which are owned and controlled by UOL, its related companies or by other parties that have licensed their material to UOL. Material on any Web site owned, operated, licensed or controlled by UOL may not be copied, reproduced, republished, modified, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, including by e-mail or other electronic means, without the express prior written consent of UOL. Use of the materials on any other Web site or networked computer environment, or use of the materials for any purpose other than personal, non-commercial use is a violation of UOL's copyrights, trademarks and other proprietary rights, and is prohibited.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIABILITY
THE MATERIALS ON UOL'S WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. UOL DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OTHER THAN THOSE WARRANTIES WHICH, UNDER THE LAWS APPLICABLE TO THIS AGREEMENT, ARE IMPLIED BY LAW AND ARE INCAPABLE OF EXCLUSION, RESTRICTION, OR MODIFICATION. NEITHER UOL, NOR ITS AFFILIATED OR RELATED ENTITIES, NOR ANY PERSON INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION OF UOL'S WEB SITE WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIALS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT UOL OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THEM AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. THE MATERIAL THAT YOU READ ON UOL'S WEB SITE IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL AND PROMOTIONAL PURPOSES. UOL DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE MATERIALS IN UOL'S WEB SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE.
YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT USE OF THE UOL SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT NEITHER UOL, NOR ITS AFFILIATED OR RELATED ENTITIES, NOR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS, NOR ANY PERSON OR ENTITY INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION OF UOL'S WEB SITE ARE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE TO ANY PERSON OR ENTITY WHATSOEVER FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGE (WHETHER ACTUAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHERWISE), INJURY, CLAIM, LIABILITY OR OTHER CAUSE OF ANY KIND OR CHARACTER WHATSOEVER BASED UPON OR RESULTING FROM THE USE OR MISUSE OF THIS SITE OR ANY OTHER UOL WEB SITE. BY WAY OF EXAMPLE, AND WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, UOL AND RELATED PERSONS AND ENTITIES SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM OR DAMAGE ARISING FROM FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION, COMPUTER VIRUS, THEFT, DESTRUCTION, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF PERSONAL RECORDS, OR THE RELIANCE UPON OR USE OF DATA, INFORMATION, OPINIONS OR OTHER MATERIALS APPEARING ON THIS SITE. YOU (AND NOT UOL) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF, AND RESPONSIBILITY FOR, ANY AND ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THIS SITE. IN ADDITION, YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT UOL IS NOT LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF OTHER USERS OR THIRD PARTIES.
Information Updates
Materials contained on this site or in links from the site are dated as of the date originally issued or posted and may no longer be accurate. UOL has no obligation to ensure that any information posted to this site is either timely or accurate, meaning that errors may appear from time to time and certain information may not be the most current information available. While follow-up information and reports may be posted, the site may continue to provide access to the original information and reports, as in an archive of press releases, for example, and UOL may not change the original report to reflect the new developments. Individuals looking for the most recent information should be sure that they are not accessing an outdated report. Before acting on information found on the site, facts that are important to a decision should be independently confirmed. UOL assumes no obligation to update any materials.
Jurisdictional Issues
These Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, excluding its conflict of laws principles. The exclusive personal jurisdiction of and venue for all disputes arising out of these Rules shall be the state and federal courts located in Los Angeles, California, USA and you consent to such exclusive jurisdiction and waive all objections to such jurisdiction and venue.
Privacy
UOL is very respectful about the privacy concerns of the visitors to its sites on the Internet. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from visitors to this site. However, certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard operation of UOL's Internet servers. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable data about visitors to this site are known to UOL only when voluntarily submitted by the users. UOL will only use personally identifiable data provided at this site for the purposes described at the time it is collected (for example, the e-mail addresses visitors provide in order to receive e-mail alerts will only be used for the purpose of sending these e-mail alerts). The information we collect from users is processed and maintained in the United States, where privacy laws may not be as protective as in your home country. If you are using our Web site from outside of the United States, by providing information to us you are consenting to the transfer of the information to the United States for processing in a manner consistent with these Terms of Use. UOL sites, as well as any other third party sites linked to or from this Web site, may each have different privacy policies and practices. You should carefully review these other Web sites' privacy policies in order to determine how each site may use any personal information you provide.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
Cookies and other Technical Information
We may send "cookies" to your computer. "Cookies" are files that can identify you as a unique user and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data). Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). We may also use "Web beacons" that monitor your use of our sites. Web beacons are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.
On their own, cookies or Web beacons do not contain or reveal any personally identifiable information. However, if you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information can be linked to the data stored in the cookies/Web beacons.
By accepting these Terms of Use, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and Web beacons. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Additionally, by setting your Web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons.
Sitemap
Terms of Use
Postmaster
© 2001-2020 United Online, Inc. United Online is a registered trademark and the United Online logo is a trademark ofUnited Online, Inc.
